hi my name is Joe brewer and I'm really
excited to share with you my newest
crowdfunding campaign this one is
partnering with the awesome nonprofit
organization sustainable Seattle so what
we're doing is offering a three-part
workshop series later this year on how
to bring about large-scale behavior
change now as part of that workshop I
would really like to take the course
materials that we put together and turn
them into a standalone educational
resource when I'm calling a designer's
manual for large-scale change and that's
what we want to accomplish with this
crowdfunding campaign so basically
here's video we want to raise five
thousand dollars so that we can take the
curriculum that's being developed for
the workshop and turn it into something
that stand alone for anyone in the world
to take and use and of course since the
cloud pays for it the crowd will get to
own it so that means that will release
this design manual under a Creative
Commons license so if you want to see
this handbook get created if you'd like
to be able to use it yourself or to see
others get the opportunity to learn
alongside the participants of the
workshops please contribute now thank
you